Hanif Adedotun

Abuja, Federal Capital Territory, Nigeria



hanif.adedotun@gmail.com



09096281736



linkedin.com/in/hanif-adedotun

Summary

I am a technology enthusiast, a fast learner and I have a never ending quest to learn new things everyday. I work well with people and I pay great attention to details.

I am a full stack developer and a graphics designer.

I am currently researching on Machine learning, Blockchain technology and the Internet of Things.

I have been programming for about 3 years, during which i have developed projects which are available on my GitHub account below.

Experience



Intern

Utility Ware

Mar 2021 - Sep 2021 (7 months)

I worked on some internal projects for the company,

Contributed to the frontend of their upcoming internship dedicated website with my team,

As a team lead, we simulated an application store and its console similar to play store.

Graphic Designer

The future designs

May 2018 - Sep 2019 (1 year 5 months)

I worked mainly as a graphics designer, but i also worked on projects as a full stack programmer. As a company we worked on some number of applications, web design, graphics design and robotics. Our pioneer app is the auto text.

Education

Nile University of Nigeria

Computer Engineering, Computer Software Engineering 2019 - 2024

Licenses & Certifications



Internet of Things Intro - IBM

https://www.youracclaim.com/badges/e16b14f5-2b1c-4aa9-b1d0-c9a7b378c8ed/linked_i



Blockchain intro - IBM



AWS Concepts - Udemy

101r3GAEMZdVhbTH8C

- introduction to Data Science using Python Udemy 101rPyAEMZdVhbTH8C
- Microsoft Office Specialist: Microsoft Office PowerPoint 2016 Microsoft wUyMU-HahK
- Microsoft Office Specialist: Microsoft Office Excel 2013 Microsoft dsR7-XVme
- Artificial Intelligence Intro IBM https://www.credly.com/badges/a964634c-5205-4059-929b-333668281ed1/public_url

Skills

Node.js • React.js • MySQL • Robotics • Database Design • Artificial Intelligence (AI) • Big Data • Android Development • PHP • HTML